(gentle music)
If you're required to complete a selling application
for a product in the Amazon store,
it's essential to provide clear pictures
of your physical product and its packaging.
These images will be reviewed by Amazon
to help verify that your product meets
all necessary requirements,
including proper labeling, safety standards,
and category specific criteria.
You will need to include front and back images
of your product and packaging,
or from all sides if you're requesting a GTIN exemption,
and ensure that your images clearly show
a permanently attached product label
that displays the brand owner
or manufacturer's name and current contact information
that includes either a complete physical address,
a website URL, or a phone number.
Additionally, all label information such as the branding,
product name or ingredients must be clearly visible
and easy to read.
You may use a smartphone camera to capture your images
since they are solely for application review
and won't appear on product detail pages.
Note that we won't accept stock images,
digitally altered or computer generated mockups
in place of photos you take yourself.
Before submitting your images,
be sure to check that each picture
matches the exact product and country or region
that you're applying to sell in.
During the application review process,
Amazon may contact you if additional information is needed.
To find more details for products or categories
requiring approval in Seller Central,
you can search for and review the categories
and products that require approval help page.